# ANA TRIPUNOSKA ZDRAVKOVIKJ

# Front-End Developer

(M) +389 70 777 044

atripunoska.github.io

atripunoska@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Passionate and meticulous front-end developer with over 5 years of front end experience, striving for continuous self-improvement and making the internet a better (looking) place. Primary focus on converting data to graphical interface for users to view and interact with that data, through digital interaction using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

March 2016 - Present

#### **IWM NETWORK**

- Using markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages
- Maintaining and improving websites
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- PSD to HTML
- Developing custom WordPress Themes
- Developing custom Liferay Themes
- Developing e-commerce websites using WooCommerce for selling products online
- Strong experience with Responsive website design
- Implementing On-Page SEO

#### INTERN

August 2015 - September 2015

### **IBORN.NET**

- Maintaining Web Applications
- Designing mobile based features
- Writing functional required documents and guides

#### INTERN

September 2014 -May 2015

#### **DUNA COMPUTERS**

- Maintaining Web Applications
- Creating Web Application with Bootstrap
- Creating CSS files for websites and assist web developers in effective implementation
- Testing websites and reporting bugs

#### INTERN

#### KOMERCIJALNA BANKA

January 2013 - February 2013

Managing the database

 Writing SQL queries to insert, modify and delete data in database

## **EDUCATION**

MASTER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

2018 - Present

- FACULTY OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING SS. CYRIL AND METHODIUS UNIVERSITY

# **SKILLS**

#### **TECHNICAL**

HTML/HTML5
CSS/CSS3
JAVASCRIPT
BOOTSTRAP
LESS/SASS
WORDPRESS
GIT
PHOTOSHOP
WOOCOMMERCE
PHP

# PERSONAL

TEAM WORK
WORK ETHIC
ADAPTABILITY
PROBLEM
SOLVING
COMMUNICATION
LISTENING

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### **MACEDONIAN**

NATIVE

# ENGLISH

BILINGUAL

### SPANISH

CONVERSATIONAL - LEVEL A2

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

CAMBRIDGE ENGLISH: FIRST (FCE)

GRADE B

**ONLINE MARKETING FUNDAMENTALS** 

2018

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING - FACULTY OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING SS. CYRIL AND METHODIUS UNIVERSITY